melodyloops.com 2019-06-16

# Privacy Policy

Effective from May 2018

**How to get in touch**

You can get in touch with MelodyLoops.com in relation to this privacy policy via email, [support@melodyloops.com](mailto:support@melodyloops.com). Alternatively, you can write us at: Melody Loops LP, Suite 4082, Mitchell House, 5 Mitchell Street, Edinburgh, EH6 78D, Scotland, UK.

Our company number is SL024553.

MelodyLoops.com may make changes to this Privacy Policy at its sole discretion. If we make changes, we will post them on our site. Please revisit this page to stay informed of the current policy and any changes. Any changes will be reflected in the "effective date" above. 

**The information we collect and why we collect it**

MelodyLoops.com collects the following information in order to administer your account and provide you with the services offered on our website:

  * Name
  * Email
  * Payment details 

The provision of the above personal data, forms part of the contractual obligations we have with you. Without this information, we would not be able to provide you with the services you have requested from us. 

We also collect non-personally identifiable information when you visit our website (MelodyLoops.com). This data includes URL of the website that sent you to the MelodyLoops.com main page, browser cookie and browser type. This data is automatically recorded in our server logs and is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the MelodyLoops.com website and services. 

Additionally, MelodyLoops.com will not use personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent except as part of a specific program or feature for which you have explicitly opted-in to, and will have the ability to opt-out of at any time.

MelodyLoops.com uses non-personally identifiable information so that, we can:

  * Improve the quality and design of our website and services and to create new features and functionality
  * Monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns
  * Monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.

**Where your information is stored**

The information you provide us is stored on our secure servers in the United States of America. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be considered 100% secure. However, MelodyLoops.com takes all reasonable technical and organisational measures to protect your privacy and security. While making orders or working with your account, MelodyLoops.com uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. 

We also safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access, through access control procedures, network firewalls and physical security measures. Further, MelodyLoops.com retains your personal information only as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes of administering your account, or as required by law.

**Your rights**

Under the Data Protection Act (2018) you have the right to:

  * Request a copy of your personal data which we store
  * Request that your personal data is updated or corrected
  * Request the deletion of all your data (in some instances)
  * Request the restriction of the processing of you information
  * Request that the data we hold on you is transferred to another organisations
  * Withdraw your consent regarding the processing of your personal data at any time

If you are unhappy with the way we use your personal data, you have the right to complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO). You can contact the ICO by telephone on: 0303 123 1113.

If you wish to request any of the above information, please send an e-mail to: [support@melodyloops.com](mailto:support@melodyloops.com). Alternatively, you can write us at: Melody Loops LP, Suite 4082, Mitchell House, 5 Mitchell Street, Edinburgh, EH6 78D, Scotland, UK.
